Anthony Magana

Oakland, CA | (510) 850 - 6091 | anthony.ch.magana@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Friendly and efficient service professional with a background in customer service and food service roles. Experienced in front counter service, handling customer inquiries, and performing various kitchen tasks. Excellent communication and organizational skills with a focus on providing outstanding customer experiences.

Relevant Experience

Royal Coffee Inc. Custodian May 2024 – Present Oakland, CA	 Cleans, mops, vacuums, and assists with maintenance at 2 locations Responsible for assisting with daily cleanup of a two story office and a cafe
Animoto Inc. Senior Customer Advisor Jul 2018 – Feb 2022 New York, NY	 Worked with thousands of customers to handle service disputes and collect feedback Created processes for helping customers more efficiently and trained team members to pass on skills
Thinkful Inc. Student Support Manager Jul 2017 - April 2018 New York, NY	 Liaison between management, contractors, and student customers to ensure successful adoption of services Supported the community by answering technical questions, and resolving service disputes Various executive assistant duties and contractor payroll
Square Inc. Customer Support Representative Jul 2016 - Apr 2017 San Francisco, CA	 Provided exceptional customer support, addressing inquiries and resolving issues related to Square's POS hardware Assisted customers with payment processing and account management, ensuring a seamless experience

Holiday Inn Express Front Desk Agent/Night Auditor Feb 2016 - Jul 2016 Oakland, CA	 Provided world-class guest services for up to 100 guest reservations per day Audited and produced nightly reports for the general manager
SRO Fine Foods Foodservice Staff Nov 2015 - Dec 2015 Scarsdale, NY	 Managed and fulfilled catering orders for the winter holidays Took and prepared orders for sandwiches, salads, and other pre-prepared specialties Reset coffee, oatmeal, soup, and salad bar fixings
Denali Organic Growers Farmhand (through W.O.O.F.) Aug 2015 - Sept 2015 Healy, AK	 Volunteered in a farmer education program and harvested vegetables Learned homesteading and community farming skills, packaged food for CSA programs and farmers markets
Gargiulos Waiter May 2015 - July 2015 Brooklyn, NY	Provided professional waiting and catering services in a banquet hall setting
Coals Pizzeria Shift Lead Sept 2014 - May 2015 Bronxville, NY	 Supervised front counter staff and operations, trained new hires and bartended during peak hours Coordinated with the kitchen for timely orders, handled register and financial reporting Served as a bartender, handled register and financial reporting
Sarah Lawrence College Student Shuttle Driver Jan 2014 - Nov 2014 Bronxville, NY	 Taxied students around campus in an on-call capacity Drove a full-size passenger van, taxied students around campus and to various field trips and sports games around the tri-state area

Education

Laney College, Oakland, CA
Sept 2019: Associate of Arts Degree